你最近在研究什么呢?
So, what are you working on these days?
我在研究单细胞微生物
I'm studying one-celled organisms
想找找看能引起羞耻感的
to try and find the neurochemicals
神经化学机制
that lead to the feeling of shame.
一个单细胞微生物有什么好羞耻的?
What would a one-celled organism have to be embarrassed about?
跟我们一样 没穿内衣就下车才会羞耻
Same as all of us, getting out of a car without underwear.
说到内衣
Speaking of underwear,
我有些有趣的事...
I have some interesting news...
好吧 如果是Howie穿了你内衣那事
Okay, if it's sometimes Howie wears yours,
Leonard已经告诉我们了
Leonard already told us.
他只是想搞笑
He was being funny.
我很确定
I'm pretty sure.
话说回来 我被邀请接受采访
Anyway, I was asked to be a part of a magazine article
那是篇关于加州五十位最性感女科学家的杂志报道
about the 50 sexiest female scientists in California.
很不错吧?
Isn't that cool?
我觉得糟透了
I think it's awful.
你为什么这么说?
Why would you say that?
Bernadette是个很成功的微生物学家
Bernadette is a successful microbiologist.
别人关注的应该是她的成就 而非长相
She should be celebrated for her achievements, not her looks.
我是说那会传达什么信息呢?
I mean, what kind of message does that send?
我觉得会是... "都来看看那漂亮的科学家"
I think the message is... "check out the rack on that scientist."
为什么一个人就不能智慧和美貌并存呢?
Why can't someone be thought of as both smart and pretty?
我只是觉得一个职业女性不应该通过
I just don't think a professional woman should have
夸耀自己的性别 换取出名的机会
to flaunt her sexuality in order to get ahead.
那又有什么关系?
Okay, what's the big deal?
听着 如果能帮我说服医师买我的药
Look, if it helps me make a sale with a physician,
我觉得稍微调调情也无伤大雅
I don't think it hurts to flirt a little.
比如他们说笑话的时候笑笑 搭着他们的手臂
I mean, laugh at their joke, touch their arm,
也许可以提前打开车里的空调
maybe crank up the AC in the car beforehand, you know,
秀一秀事业线
to wake up the girls.
也许销售行业不一样
Maybe it's different in the world of sales,
但在科学领域
but it's already hard enough
已经很难人别人把女科学家当回事了
for women to be taken seriously in science.
我本来听说采访还挺兴奋的
I was kind of excited about the article,
但现在你让我觉得糟透了
but now you're making me feel bad.
不 我觉得你应该做想做的事情
No, I think you should do whatever you want.
要是时尚杂志里面
You know, maybe if fashion magazines had
有女科学家的话
female scientists in them,
我早就去当理论物理学家了
I would've become a theoretical physicist.
不准相视一笑
Stop smirking at each other.
* 宇宙一度又烫又稠密 *
* Our whole universe was in a hot, dense state *
* 140亿年前终于爆了炸... 等着瞧! *
* Then nearly 14 billion years ago expansion started... Wait! *
* 地球开始降温 *
* The Earth began to cool *
* 自养生物来起哄 穴居人发明工具 *
* The autotrophs began to drool, Neanderthals developed tools *
* 我们建长城 我们建金字塔 *
* We built the Wall We built the pyramids *
* 数学 自然科学 历史 揭开神秘 *
* Math, Science, History, unraveling the mystery *
* 一切由大爆炸开始 *
* That all started with a big bang *
生活大爆炸 第八季第7集
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 影子   时间轴: pisces夜
翻译: 酱油影 凤梨酥 Astral   校对: UU爆炸了
谢谢
Thank you.
不 应该谢谢你
No, thank you.
快递员是人们忘记赞美的
Delivery men are the unsung foot soldiers
我国贸易领域的步兵
of our nation's commerce.
正是有了你们这样的人
It's because of people like you,
我这样的人才能减少与他人接触
people like me can limit our human contact.
我想跟你握手的 不过还是算了吧
I'd shake your hand, but, well, you know.
我不是快递员 我... 是医生
I'm not a delivery man, I... I'm a doctor.
虽然我的确经常给患者
Although I do often deliver
送紧急活体检验报告
alarming biopsy results to my patients.
你真幽默
That's humorous.
好吧
All right.
我... 打赌你给患者缝针
Yeah, I... I bet you leave your patients in stitches.
我也挺幽默的
That was also humorous.
好吧
All right.
你带花给病人
Are you bringing flowers to a patient
是为了缓解末期诊断的打击吗?
to cushion the blow of a terminal diagnosis?
刚才那个不是笑话
That wasn't a joke.
好吧
All right.
这话是给一位打销售电话
These are actually for a nice woman
到我办公室的优秀女人的
who makes sales calls to my office.
恩
Hmm.
要知道 这事有快递员
You know, they have delivery people
可以帮你做的
that will do that for you.
我想通过上网人肉她
I was hoping to impress her
突然出现在她家门口
by tracking her down on the Internet
给她留个好印象
and then showing up unannounced at her door.
特别努力一把
Making the extra effort.
祝你好运
Good for you.
正好 外卖刚到
Great timing, food just got here.
- 哦 Siam Palace的?  - 没错
- Ooh, Siam Palace?  - Yes.
- 炒米粉和沙爹鸡?  - 没错
- Uh, mee krob and chicken satay?  - Yes.
- 多加了花生酱?  - 没有 不过你可以吃我的
- Uh, extra peanut sauce?  - No, but you can have mine.
好 很好
Eh, well, very well.
说到要分享你的事情
Oh, and on the topic of sharing things that are yours,
现在有位男士
there is a gentleman caller
正在给你的未婚妻送花
bringing flowers to your fiancee as we speak.
什么?
What?
你干嘛不先说?
Why didn't you say that first?
你干嘛不给我多拿花生酱?
Why didn't you get extra peanut sauce?
我们都可以这么玩
We can both play this game.
有什么事吗?
Can I help you?
你好
Oh, hi.
Penny住这里吗?
Uh, does Penny live here?
有什么事吗?
May I ask why?
呃...
Well, uh...
我... 是在办公室认识她的 她对我抛了媚眼
I... I met her at my office, she winked at me.
所以...
And, uh...
我来... 是想开始一段浪漫的感情
I... I came hoping to initiate a romantic relationship.
好吧...
Okay, um...
听着 我很确定她没对你抛媚眼
Look, I'm pretty sure she didn't wink at you.
她抛了
Oh, she did.
像这样 超诱惑
Seductively, like this.
然后她搭了我的手臂两秒钟
And then she touched my arm for two Mississippis.
就像这样 一秒 两秒...
Like, you know, one Mississippi, two...
我懂了 我懂了
I got it, I got it.
听着...
Listen, um...
我觉得你肯定是误会了
I think there's been a misunderstanding.
Penny是我的未婚妻
See, Penny is my fiancee.
真的?
Really?
但我没看她戴订婚戒指呀
I've never seen her wear an engagement ring.
真的?
Really?
那我可以认为
So, am I to presume
她的调情是一种销售手段吗?
that her flirtation was just a sales technique?
就是这样
I think so.
我什么时候才能吸取教训?
When will I learn?
跟上次宠物店可爱女孩的时候完全一样
It's just like the cute girl at the pet store all over again.
你说什么?
Excuse me?
她搭了我的手臂五秒钟
Oh, uh, she touched my arm for five Mississippis,
我就买了套两千块的鬣鳞蜥饲养缸
and I bought a $2,000 iguana habitat.
结果她一直说忙 都不来看看
Which she was always too busy to come over and see.
请把这个给Penny
You give these to Penny.
你真是个幸运的男人
You're, you're a lucky man.
谢谢
Thank you.
抱歉
Sorry.
哦...
Oh, uh...
你大概不想让她看到这个
you probably don't want her to see this.
里面的图生动过头了
It's unnecessarily graphic.
等等 医生
Hold on, Doctor.
Leonard 你的社交礼仪哪儿去了?
Leonard, where are your social skills?
这位先生显然很伤心
This man is clearly upset.
我们应该请他进去喝杯热饮
We should invite him in for a hot beverage.
他想勾搭Penny
He tried to score with Penny.
这两位也勾搭过 他们还跟我们吃完饭呢
So have these two, and they're having dinner with us.
今天工作怎么样?
So, how was work today?
不错 但你应该会很高兴
It was fine, but you'll be happy to know
他们撤消了那篇性感科学家的报道
they pulled the sexy scientists article.
怎么了?
What happened?
我也不知道
I don't know.
他们取消了拍摄
They just canceled the photo shoot
说要再考虑一下
and said they're rethinking it.
真的很抱歉
Well, I'm really sorry,
不过我觉得这样最好
but I think it's for the best.
你应该希望人们更关注你的学术成就
You want people focusing on your achievements,
而不是盯着杂志看你的胸
not staring at your breasts in some magazine.
我知道
I guess.
这真的不重要
It's really not that important.
嘿 别看了
Hey, up here.
不好意思... 说着说着就看上了
Sorry, we're... we were talking about them.
其实... 我本来不打算告诉你的
So, look, I... I wasn't going to say anything,
不过既然你对撤稿这件事看的这么开
but since you seem to be okay with the article being canceled,
我觉得应该告诉你实话
I have a little confession.
是我让他们撤下这篇文章的
I'm the reason it was pulled.
什么? 怎么回事?
What? How?
我给杂志编辑
I sent the editors of the magazine
写了一封言辞激烈的邮件
a pretty scathing e-mail.
Amy 你说了什么?
Amy, what did you say?
我不过是指出
I simply pointed out
他们绝对不会发表一篇
that they would never consider doing an article
男科学家性感程度的排名
ranking male scientists on their sexuality,
更不可能拍他们暴露身体的照片
let alone showing them in various stages of undress.
因为没人会愿意看Neil deGrasse Tyson(美国男科学家)
Because no one wants to see Neil deGrasse Tyson
穿着湿T恤在保时捷车旁边凹造型
in a wet T-shirt, bent over the hood of a Porsche.
无所谓啦
Well, it doesn't make a difference,
反正他们也觉得这样不太好
because they agreed it was in bad taste,
而且现在你也同意了 所以...
and now you agree, so...
Amy做得对哦
Amy saves the day.
不 是你嫉妒我了
No, what happened was you got jealous,
所以你夺走了让我增加曝光率的一个机会
so you took away a chance for me to get some publicity.
又不是好曝光
But it was bad publicity.
那也是我来决定 不是你
That's for me to decide, not you.
我不同意
I disagree.
作为一名女性科学家 你的所作所为也会影响到我们其他人
As a female scientist, I think what you do affects all of us.
可是我觉得你不喜欢别人
And I think you don't like people
展示她们性感的一面
expressing their sexuality
是因为没人觉得你性感
because no one wants you to express yours.
Amy 不好意思
Oh, Amy, I'm so sorry.
我太过分了
That was over the line.
你自己好好待着吧
You have a nice night.
求求你 别走啊
Please don't go.
就算我说的有点过分 也是你不对在先的
Up until my vicious attack, you were the one in the wrong.
给你 医生
Here you go, Doctor.
这是加了一勺蜂蜜的热花茶
Red Zinger with one teaspoon of honey.
谢谢
Thank you.
星际迷航的马克杯 不错嘛
Neat Star Trek mug.
其实我有一个原版电视剧里
I actually have one of the phasers
演员们用的那个杯子
from the original TV show.
这么酷炫
Oh, cool.
你怎么拿到的?
How'd you get that?
简单的很 Gene Roddenberry要做切除输精管的手术
Oh, easy, Gene Roddenberry needed a vasectomy.
等下
Wait a minute.
你剪过Gene Roddenberry的输精管?
You've snipped Gene Roddenberry's vas deferens?
对啊
Yes.
哇哦 他还真是到过无人之境啊
Wow, he really went where no man has gone before.
不是我爱吹牛 可是
I don't like to brag, but, uh, you see,
我是个专为明星做泌尿系统手术的医生
I'm kind of the doctor to the stars' urinary tracts.
哇哦
Wow.
诶 你们要不要看看詹姆斯·卡梅隆的肾结石?
Uh, you, you want to see James Cameron's kidney stone?
嗷啊
Ooh.
手术之后他特别开心 就给了我一个终结者
He was so happy after he passed it, he gave me a Terminator.
太赞了啊
That is amazing.
你收集这些东西有多久了?
How long have you been collecting?
我从小就开始收集这些东西
Ever since I was a kid,
不过直到William Shatner膀胱感染的时候
but, uh, I didn't really get serious
才开始对收藏认真起来
until William Shatner's bladder infection.
你那次拿到了什么? 拿到了什么?
What'd you get? What'd you get?
他说那是星际迷航里的Tribble小毛球
Well, he said it was a Tribble.
也没准是假发呢
It could be a toupee,
不过不管怎么说都蛮不错啦
but either way, it's pretty cool.
我... 我好想去看看你的藏品啊
I... I would love to see your collection.
随时欢迎
Anytime.
我那确实还有不少好东西
Uh, I've got some cool stuff.
最开始的时候
When I first started,
我以为收集这些东西能帮我泡妹
I thought it would be a good way to meet women,
不过 你们懂的...
but, well, you know...
- 人艰不拆  - 我们懂的
- Sure. Preach.  - We know.
我能问你个私人问题吗?
Can I ask you a personal question?
问吧
Sure.
呃 你和我是一类人
Um, I mean, you're a guy like me,
那你是怎么追到Penny的?
so how'd you get a girl like Penny?
哦
Oh.
这个嘛 就是...
Well, you know, just...
做自己 真的
being myself, really.
快别装了!
Oh, please!
我告诉你他是怎么做的吧
You know, I'll tell you how he did it.
就是无休无止的死缠烂打
Implacable, relentless badgering.
用泌尿学术语来说
In urology terms,
他就像是有抗药性的葡萄球菌
he was a drug-resistant staph infection.
Penny是对他没有抵抗力的尿道
And she was a urethra that could not shake him.
我倒不会用病菌形容自己
I don't know that I'd call myself an infection.
真男人这时候应该觉得他的未婚妻
A gallant man would defend his fiance
不应该被说成是尿道吧
for being called a urethra.
咱们能换个话题吗?
Can we please change the subject?
嗨
Hi.
看来 这话题换不了了
Well, that didn't go your way.
Lorvis医生 你怎么会在这里?
Dr. Lorvis, what are you doing here?
呃 我其实是来找你的
Uh, well, actually I came to see you.
真的吗? 为什么啊?
Really? Why?
呃 这个问题问得好
Ah, that's a good question.
显然有些人由于在不戴订婚戒指的时候
Apparently someone was being awfully flirty
有强烈的和别人调情的嫌疑
while not wearing their engagement ring,
导致另一个人出现在这里
causing another someone to show up
而且还觉得第一个人可以成为他的女朋友
here thinking the first someone might be available.
天啊 别难为她了
Oh, God. Don't make it so hard on her.
听着 第一个人是不诚实的你
Look, the first someone is the deceitful you.
第二个人是
The second someone
超赞的Lorvis医生
is the delightful Dr. Lorvis.
哦 这太尴尬了
Oh, this is very embarrassing.
Lorvis医生 真对不起
Dr. Lorvis, I am so sorry.
我不是故意想勾引你的
I did not mean to lead you on.
你摸我胳膊摸了两秒那么久呢
You touched my arm for two Mississippis.
哦
Oh.
怪不得你当时在数数
That's why you were mumbling "Mississippi."
我们能单独谈谈吗?
Can we talk in private?
当然
Please, yes.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
那么
So what other
你还接手过哪些名人的生殖器?
celebrity genitalia have you handled?
这到底是怎么回事?
So, uh, what's the deal?
你工作的时候不戴订婚戒指?
You take off your ring when you go to work?
什么? 才不是!
What? No! No!
我就是换到另一只手上...
I just put it on the other hand and...
把戒指反过来
turn it around.
然后把手插兜里
Keep that hand in my pocket.
为什么啊?
Why?
什么叫为什么?
Well, what do you mean why?
是这样的 如果医生觉得我是单身的话
Look, I make more sales
我能卖出去更多药
if these doctors think I'm single.
我当服务生的时候也这么干过
I did the same kind of thing as a waitress.
问题在于 他在你们家里做什么?
The real question is, what is he doing in your apartment?
哦 他有点失落
Oh, he was upset.
所以Sheldon请他来家里喝热饮
So Sheldon invited him in for a hot beverage.
你觉得这样没问题吗?
You were okay with that?
不 我超级不爽!
No. I got upset!
然后Sheldon给我也做了一杯热饮
And Sheldon made me a beverage, too.
好吧 他就这样冲过来找我
Okay, he just showed up at my door.
你不觉得这样有点诡异吗?
Don't you think that's a little weird?
是有点 不过... 他还挺无害的
A little, but... he's basically harmless.
- 他其实是个好人  - 好吧
- He's actually kind of a nice guy.  - Okay.
不管怎么说 我们公司不允许我们
Whatever, look, my company does not allow me
在工作之外和医生们有私人接触
to socialize with doctors outside of work.
你赶紧把他甩了
You got to get rid of him.
为什么要我去甩?
Why am I the one that has to get rid of him?
我做不到! 他是我最好的客户!
I can't do it! He's my best client!
好吧 我去赶他
All right, I'll get rid of him.
但这算你欠我的
But you owe me one.
嘿 我们去Oliver家看他的收藏
Hey, we're going to Oliver's house to see his collection.
你想和我们一起去吗?
You want to go with us?
当然
Yeah, sure.
你欠我的
You owe me.
我的亲娘啊!
Oh, my God!
Leonard 我错了
Leonard, I was wrong.
天堂是存在的
Heaven does exist.
它在Sherman Oaks的泌尿科医师家
And it's in the basement of a urologist's house
的地下室里
in Sherman Oaks.
欢迎来到我的孤单城堡
Welcome to my Fortress of Solitude.
这是我逃避...
This is where I go to get away from...
我其他孤单时刻的地方
all my other solitude.
不是吧 肯定是个复制品
Oh, come on. It's a replica.
原版的
Original.
我感觉我刚刚肉体出轨了
Oh, I think I just cheated on my wife.
这是地狱公爵的枪?
The gun from Hellboy?
是的
Yup.
你怎么拿到的?
How did you get it?
我在一场拍卖会上买到的
Bought it at auction.
哦 我以为这里面有什么关于
Oh, I was hoping for a juicy tidbit
Ron Perlman的睾丸的有趣的故事
about Ron Perlman's testicles.
Oliver! 我要玩宾果了!
Oliver! I'm going to play bingo!
好的 妈妈 玩的开心
Okay, Mother. Have fun.
他还和他妈住一起
Still lives with his mom.
真恶心 是吧?
Yikes, right?
嗯 你这句话我真是无言以对
Yeah, I'm not quite sure how to respond.
哇 大金刚!
Wow, Donkey Kong!
这... 这是我小时候最爱的游戏!
This... this was my game when I was a kid!
因为它是一个
Because it's a story
关于一个漂亮的金发女孩
of a pretty blonde girl
被一个体型奇怪的小人坚持不懈地追求的故事?
tirelessly pursued by a small, oddly-shaped man?
不 因为我喜欢它
No, because I liked it.
别太敏感了
Well, now, don't get defensive.
虽然你体型奇怪 但是你追到女孩了啊
You're oddly-shaped, but you got the girl.
我发现Leonard经常因为
So, I've noticed Leonard gets teased a lot
他和Penny的关系被嘲弄
about his relationship with Penny.
是的 如果你想一起笑他
Yes. If you'd like to join in,
包袱就是他们的爱情看上去不靠谱 而且必然会失败
the premise is their love seems unlikely and doomed to failure.
所以 你觉得她马上就会变单身了?
So, you think she'll be single soon?
如果你想等着
Oh, if you want to get in on the pool,
那就太晚了...
you're too late...
队都排到看不见了
All the squares have been purchased.
有趣
Interesting.
不好意思 我要先走了
Excuse me, I have to take care of something.
Leonard 作为你的朋友
Leonard, as your friend I feel
- 我觉得我需要跟你说一件事  - 什么事?
- I should tell you something.  - What?
你没多要花生酱 我还是不太开心
I'm still upset about that peanut sauce.
你能扶着门吗?
Oh, could you hold the door?
- 花不错  - 谢谢
- Nice flowers.  - Thank you.
是为一个女孩准备的
They're for a girl.
我准备做出坚决不放弃的姿态
Uh, I'm being implacable and relentless.
她真幸运
Isn't she lucky?
她总是给我矛盾的信号
She keeps sending me mixed signals.
但我... 我觉得我们两个人想要的东西是一样的
But I-I think we both want the same thing.
什么?
What's that?
无私的爱
Unconditional love.
我猜所有人都想要那个吧
I guess that's all anybody wants.
我想也是
I guess so.
祝你有一天能得到它
Well, I hope you get it.
一秒 两秒
One Mississippi, two Mississippi.
下一局我们把头盔换过来玩吧
Next game, let's switch helmets.
不行 我戴着那个头盔很二
No, I'd look silly in that helmet.
我... 我不能拿这些
I-I can't take these.
为什么?
Well, why not?
你要的和我要的是一样的
I mean, you want what I want.
我们一起度过了两秒美妙的时刻
And we had two wonderful Mississippis.
但是 那个女孩怎么办?
But what about the other girl?
对哦
Oh, right.
我会告诉她
I'll tell her
我和她还是做朋友比较好
we should just be friends.
Lorvis医生 你怎么来了?
Dr. Lorvis?
Penny 我们还是只做朋友吧
Penny, we should just be friends.
高兴了吗?
Happy?
你觉得他会咬人吗?
You think he bites?
把你的手伸进去试试看
Stick your hand in there and find out.
宠物园的那头山羊那里 你就骗过我
You fooled me with that goat at the petting zoo.
你再也骗不到我了
You will not fool me again.
我在想Lorvis医生在哪里
I wonder where Dr. Lorvis is.
他已经走了有一段时间了
He's been gone a while.
他可能在和他妈咪在玩宾果
Maybe he's playing bingo with his mommy.
有些人断不了奶
It's sad how some guys
真是令人伤心
can't cut the apron strings.
现在你是跟我开玩笑吧
Okay, now you're messing with me.
额 大伙们 我们被锁在里面了
Uh, guys, we're locked in here.
哦 今天真是越来越棒了!
Oh, this day just keeps getting better!
所以你就把他们留在你家玩游戏?
So, you just left them alone playing games in your house?
他们看上去挺快乐的 而且...
Well, they seemed happy and...
我以为这样做可以
I thought that would give me time
给我一点时间 和你互相了解一下
for you and I to get to know each other better.
那是在我们见面之前的事了
That was before we met.
我们都有过去
We all have a past.
医生 你一定要明白你做的事
Doc, you've got to see what you're doing
有... 有点让人毛骨悚然
is-is a little creepy.
Sigourney Weaver说过一样的话
You sound just like Sigourney Weaver
在我跟着她走进厕所之后
when I followed her into a restroom.
好了 你们不能去追
Okay, you can't just go chasing after
所有对你们好的女孩
every girl who's nice to you.
那可不是Sheldon说的
Well, that's not what Sheldon says.
他好像在女孩子当中很吃得开
And he seems to know his way around the ladies.
嘿 Leonard 猜猜谁回来了!是Lorvis医生!
Hey, Leonard. Guess who's back! Dr. Lorvis!
好啊 你想来加入我们吗?
Yeah. You care to join us?
什么?!
What?!
你把他们锁在你的地下室里了?!
You locked them in your basement?!
其实 他们... 他们不是被锁在里面了
Well, they're, they're not locked in.
只是那个门很难开
The door just sticks.
那他们怎么才能把它打开?
Okay, so how do they unstick it?
他们需要钥匙
They'd need the key.
好的
Okay.
没 没别的事了
Nope. That's it.
我们现在就过去
We are gonna go over there right now.
你得把他们放出来
And you are going to let them out.
三秒 四秒...
Three Mississippi, four Mississippi...
快走!
Move it!
哦 幸亏你们在这里
Oh, good, you're here.
Amy 对不起
Amy, I am so sorry.
等等再说 这个怪胎把
That has to wait. This weirdo locked
- 男孩们锁在他的地下室了  - 什么?!
- the guys up in his basement.  - What?!
- 她看上去人挺好的 她是谁?  - 赶紧走
- She seems nice. Who's she?  - Just walk.
加油
You can do this.
还剩下最后一个梯子!
One ladder left!
哦耶!太棒了!
Oh-ho! Yeah! Yes!
下一关!
Next level!
- Leonard 你还好吗?  - 简直不能再好了
- Leonard, are you okay?  - Better than okay.
人生有史以来打过最爽的游戏!
I am having the game of my life!
Lorvis医生 你有什么想说的吗?
Dr. Lorvis, isn't there something you want to say?
是的
Yes.
我很抱歉把你们锁在我家里了
I'm very sorry for locking you in my home.
是的 这事做得很不地道
Yeah, that was very uncool.
拿榔头! 赶紧拿榔头!
Get the hammer! Get the hammer!
拿到了
Got it.
好了 Leonard 我们走!
Okay, Leonard, let's go!
等... 等等!
J-Just hang on!
好吧 我们要不一边等
Well, while we wait,
一边看Tobey Maguire的前列腺声像图?
would you like to see Tobey Maguire's prostate sonogram?
好啊
Sure. Yeah.
对了 我要剧透了哦
Oh, spoiler alert.
他白担心了
Uh, he was worried about nothing.